<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DigitalGeoHack</title>
    <link>https://digitalgeohack.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DigitalGeoHack</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://digitalgeohack.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Geosciences Hackathon at the Institut de Physique du Globe de Paris</title>
      <link>https://digitalgeohack.github.io/post/second-anouncement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalgeohack.github.io/post/second-anouncement/</guid>
      <description>We are excited to announce that the European Association of Geoscientists and Engineers is sponsering the hackathon! Tickets at 11,85 € are now available for the hackathon via eventbrite.
The Digital Geosciences hackathon will bring together computer scientists, machine learning specialists and geoscience experts to explore new ideas for digitalization and automation in geophysical research, exploration and industrial production processes. Two principal questions are:
 How can we use cutting edge machine learning and visualization techniques to extract new information about the subsurface?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Geosciences Hackathon - 1st Anouncement</title>
      <link>https://digitalgeohack.github.io/post/first-anouncement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalgeohack.github.io/post/first-anouncement/</guid>
      <description>We plan to host a two day hackathon at the Institut de Physique du Globe de Paris on the 15th and 16th November 2019. This two day event will focus on solving problems related to digitalisation within the subsurface software stack. We wish to bring together data engineers, data scientists, petroleum engineers and geoscientists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who we are</title>
      <link>https://digitalgeohack.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalgeohack.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>We are a collection of Earth and data scientists based in paris:
 Milena Marjanovic Matthias Meschede Fernando Villanueva Miao Yu John Armitage  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>